{"Answer": "Effect of Three Decades of Screening Mammography on Breast-Cancer Incidence\n\nTo reduce mortality , screening must detect life-threatening disease at an earlier , more curable stage . Effective cancer-screening programs therefore both increase the incidence of cancer detected at an early stage and decrease the incidence of cancer presenting at a late stage .\n\nWe used Surveillance , Epidemiology , and End Results data to examine trends from 1976 through 2008 in the incidence of early-stage breast cancer ( ductal carcinoma in situ and localized disease ) and late-stage breast cancer ( regional and distant disease ) among women 40 years of age or older .\n\nThe introduction of screening mammography in the United States has been associated with a doubling in the number of cases of early-stage breast cancer that are detected each year , from 112 to 234 cases per 100,000 women -- an absolute increase of 122 cases per 100,000 women . Concomitantly , the rate at which women present with late-stage cancer has decreased by 8 % , from 102 to 94 cases per 100,000 women -- an absolute decrease of 8 cases per 100,000 women . With the assumption of a constant underlying disease burden , only 8 of the 122 additional early-stage cancers diagnosed were expected to progress to advanced disease . After excluding the transient excess incidence associated with hormone-replacement therapy and adjusting for trends in the incidence of breast cancer among women younger than 40 years of age , we estimated that breast cancer was overdiagnosed ( i.e. , tumors were detected on screening that would never have led to clinical symptoms ) in 1.3 million U.S. women in the past 30 years . We estimated that in 2008 , breast cancer was overdiagnosed in more than 70,000 women ; this accounted for 31 % of all breast cancers diagnosed .\n\nDespite substantial increases in the number of cases of early-stage breast cancer detected , screening mammography has only marginally reduced the rate at which women present with advanced cancer . Although it is not certain which women have been affected , the imbalance suggests that there is substantial overdiagnosis , accounting for nearly a third of all newly diagnosed breast cancers , and that screening is having , at best , only a small effect on the rate of death from breast cancer .\n\n", "Topic": "breast", "Question": "NEJMoa1206809", "level": 0, "branch": "NEJMoa1206809", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"screen mammography": ["Intervention"], "breast cancer": ["Outcomes"], "three decade": ["Intervention"], "1976 through 2008": ["Intervention"], "early stage": ["Outcomes"], "late stage": ["Outcomes"], "woman": ["Participants"], "40": ["Participants"], "united states": ["Participants"], "8 %": ["Outcomes"], "8 case per 100,000": ["Outcomes"], "double": ["Outcomes"], "102 to 94": ["Outcomes"], "112 to 234": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"screen mammography": ["Intervention-general"], "breast cancer": ["Outcomes-general"], "three decade": ["Duration"], "1976 through 2008": ["Duration"], "early stage": ["Outcomes-general"], "late stage": ["Outcomes-general"], "woman": ["Sex"], "40": ["Age"], "united states": ["Location"], "8 %": ["Effect-strength"], "8 case per 100,000": ["Effect-strength"], "double": ["Effect-strength"], "102 to 94": ["Effect-strength"], "112 to 234": ["Effect-strength"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A", "A"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Age": ["A"], "Condition": [], "Location": ["A"], "Sample-size": [], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Intensity": [], "Control": [], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["A"], "Adverse-effects": [], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}, "Count": 1}, "Doggos_text": {"Sex": "The participants were women.", "Age": "The participants were 40 years of age or older.", "Location": "The participants were from the United States.", "Intervention-general": "The study assessed the impact of screening mammography.", "Duration": "The screening mammography was offered for three decades (from 1976 to 2008).", "Outcomes-general": "The study measured the occurrences of early and late-stage breast cancers.", "Effect-strength": "The introduction of screening mammography was associated with a doubling in the number of cases of early stage breast cancer (from 112 to 234 cases per 100,000 women). The rate at which women present with late-stage breast cancer decreased by 8% (an absolute decrease of 8 cases per 100,000 women).", "Conclusion-general": "Despite substantial increases in the number of cases of early-stage breast cancer detected, screening mammography has only marginally reduced the rate at which women present with advanced cancer. This imbalance suggests that there is a substantial overdiagnosis."}, "id": "NEJMoa1206809", "children": [{"Answer": "While mammography is the preferred choice in detecting an early incidence of breast cancer in women, a study performed over three decades is showing some dramatic results. Effective cancer screening programs show both a substantial increase in the number of cases detected in early stages, and a decrease in cancer presenting itself at a later stage.  Since mammography was introduced in the U.S., the number of early stage cancer cases detected had doubled in just one year, while late stage cases declined.  Based on variables such as hormone-replacement therapy and other adjusted trends, the study concluded that breast cancer was overdiagnosed in 1.3 million women in the U.S. in the past 30 years. This has led researchers to believe that while screening is important, it has only marginally reduced the rate at which women are diagnosed with advanced cancer.  The imbalance suggests that overdiagnosis accounts for nearly a third of all newly diagnosed breast cancers. Screening has only a small effect on the death rate from the disease.", "AssignmentId": "3CP1TO84PUMBK9WVNO0PN8GZ3KG25Z", "Question": "NEJMoa1206809", "WorkerId": "A2KROBPV0YPE4A", "Qualification": 0.7692307692307693, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 0, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 1, "branch": "NEJMoa1206809", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"breast cancer": ["Outcomes"], "three decade": ["Intervention"], "early stage": ["Outcomes"], "late stage": ["Outcomes"], "woman": ["Participants"], "double": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"breast cancer": ["Outcomes-general"], "three decade": ["Duration"], "early stage": ["Outcomes-general"], "late stage": ["Outcomes-general"], "woman": ["Sex"], "double": ["Effect-strength"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "C", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "B"], "Outcomes": ["A", "B"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Age": ["C"], "Location": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["B"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1206809_3CP1TO84PUMBK9WVNO0PN8GZ3KG25Z", "children": [{"Answer": "The effects of three decades of screening mammography on breast cancer Incidence is still unclear. Although many cancers are found earlier in women typically starting at age 40, it is unclear if it has been helpful. A study collected data from three different types of tests, Surveillance, Epidemiology and End result data from 1976 to 2008. Although mammography does detect breast cancer at an earlier stage, It may not help decrease the incidence of late stage breast cancer. ", "AssignmentId": "31Q0U3WYDQ0JISSISDF8G9KQ32Q17Q", "Question": "NEJMoa1206809", "WorkerId": "A2LTOS0AZ3B28A", "Qualification": 0.8461538461538461, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 1, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 2, "branch": "NEJMoa1206809", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"screen mammography": ["Intervention"], "breast cancer": ["Outcomes"], "three decade": ["Intervention"], "early stage": ["Outcomes"], "late stage": ["Outcomes"], "woman": ["Participants"], "40": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"screen mammography": ["Intervention-general"], "breast cancer": ["Outcomes-general"], "three decade": ["Duration"], "early stage": ["Outcomes-general"], "late stage": ["Outcomes-general"], "woman": ["Sex"], "40": ["Age"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["B", "A", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A", "C"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["B"], "Age": ["A"], "Location": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1206809_31Q0U3WYDQ0JISSISDF8G9KQ32Q17Q", "children": [{"Answer": "The study of screening mammography has shown that it helps detect breast cancer at an earlier satge, thus preventing death among women. 112 to 234 cases per 100,00 women are detected each year. Detection at this early stage saves many more women then not.", "AssignmentId": "3OE22WJIGJ99X7OVQ0YYR26IJY4UQN", "Question": "NEJMoa1206809", "WorkerId": "A2LTOS0AZ3B28A", "Qualification": 0.8461538461538461, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 2, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 3, "branch": "NEJMoa1206809", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"screen mammography": ["Intervention"], "breast cancer": ["Outcomes"], "early stage": ["Outcomes"], "woman": ["Participants"], "112 to 234": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"screen mammography": ["Intervention-general"], "breast cancer": ["Outcomes-general"], "early stage": ["Outcomes-general"], "woman": ["Sex"], "112 to 234": ["Effect-strength"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B", "B"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Age": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Effect-strength": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1206809_3OE22WJIGJ99X7OVQ0YYR26IJY4UQN", "children": [{"Answer": "Breast cancer screening has had a small effect in reduction of the disease by catching cancers early, but had also led to overdiagnosis.", "AssignmentId": "369J354OFEVXI74GRMVJHIO0AVKG6V", "Question": "NEJMoa1206809", "WorkerId": "A6CVN7CSC1K26", "Qualification": 0.8461538461538461, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 3, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "24-39", "level": 4, "branch": "NEJMoa1206809", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"breast cancer": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"breast cancer": ["Outcomes-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["B", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B", "C"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Age": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["B"], "Duration": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1206809_369J354OFEVXI74GRMVJHIO0AVKG6V", "children": [{"Answer": "Mammogram only marginally reduce rate at which women present w/ advanced ca", "AssignmentId": "33F859I567YHOFGM7JU9DYMT350BHK", "Question": "NEJMoa1206809", "WorkerId": "A98E8M4QLI9RS", "Qualification": 1.0, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 4, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 5, "branch": "NEJMoa1206809", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"woman": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"woman": ["Sex"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["B", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["B", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B", "C"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["B"], "Age": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["B"], "Duration": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1206809_33F859I567YHOFGM7JU9DYMT350BHK"}]}]}]}]}, {"Answer": "Effective cancer-screening programs increase the incidence of cancer detection at an early stage and decrease the incidence of cancer presenting at a late stage. Surveillance, Epidemiology and end results data among women 40 yrs or older was used to examine trends from 1976 thru 2008 in the incidence of early-state breast cancer (ductal carcinoma in situ and localized) and late-stage breast cancer (regional and distant). The introduction of screening mammography in the US has been linked with doubling the number of cases of early-state breast cancer that are detected each yr, from 112 to 234 cases per 100,000 women. The rate women present w/ late-state cancer has decreased by 8%, from 102 to 94 cases per 100,000. It was estimated that breast cancer was overdiagnosed in 1.3 million US women in the past 30 yrs. In 2008, breast cancer was overdiagnosed in more than 70000 women, that is 31% of all breast cancers diagnosed. Despite increases in the number of early-state breast cancer found, screening mammograms has only marginally reduced the rate where women present with advance cancer. ", "AssignmentId": "373ERPL3YPTU9VO63AXORWULWPWRTT", "Question": "NEJMoa1206809", "WorkerId": "A98E8M4QLI9RS", "Qualification": 1.0, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 0, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 1, "branch": "NEJMoa1206809", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"screen mammography": ["Intervention"], "breast cancer": ["Outcomes"], "early stage": ["Outcomes"], "late stage": ["Outcomes"], "woman": ["Participants"], "40": ["Participants"], "8 %": ["Outcomes"], "double": ["Outcomes"], "102 to 94": ["Outcomes"], "112 to 234": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"screen mammography": ["Intervention-general"], "breast cancer": ["Outcomes-general"], "early stage": ["Outcomes-general"], "late stage": ["Outcomes-general"], "woman": ["Sex"], "40": ["Age"], "8 %": ["Effect-strength"], "double": ["Effect-strength"], "102 to 94": ["Effect-strength"], "112 to 234": ["Effect-strength"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A", "A"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Age": ["A"], "Location": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["A"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1206809_373ERPL3YPTU9VO63AXORWULWPWRTT", "children": [{"Answer": "A study in the United States on mammography screening of breast-cancer incidence from 1976 to 2008 found that the detection of early-stage breast cancer has doubled from 112 to 234 cases per 100,000 women 40 years or older. However, the rate at which women present with late-stage cancer has only decreased by 8% from 102 to 94 cases per 100,000 women. This imbalance suggests that there is substantial overdiagnosis, accounting for nearly a third of all new diagnosed breast cancers. Screenings have only a small effect on the rate of death.    ", "AssignmentId": "38JBBYETQPVLJ64B23CGKHJA197E45", "Question": "NEJMoa1206809", "WorkerId": "A3D8ZG1VV5FO35", "Qualification": 0.8461538461538461, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 1, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 2, "branch": "NEJMoa1206809", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"breast cancer": ["Outcomes"], "early stage": ["Outcomes"], "late stage": ["Outcomes"], "woman": ["Participants"], "40": ["Participants"], "united states": ["Participants"], "8 %": ["Outcomes"], "double": ["Outcomes"], "102 to 94": ["Outcomes"], "112 to 234": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"breast cancer": ["Outcomes-general"], "early stage": ["Outcomes-general"], "late stage": ["Outcomes-general"], "woman": ["Sex"], "40": ["Age"], "united states": ["Location"], "8 %": ["Effect-strength"], "double": ["Effect-strength"], "102 to 94": ["Effect-strength"], "112 to 234": ["Effect-strength"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A", "A"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Age": ["A"], "Location": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["A"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1206809_38JBBYETQPVLJ64B23CGKHJA197E45", "children": [{"Answer": "By looking at over 3 decades of breast cancer data among women 40 or over, researchers determined that screening mammography had only slightly reduced the rate of advanced breast cancers and has barely changed the rate of breast cancer deaths.  ", "AssignmentId": "3VAR3R6G1QM8EY428K5P65TT76XO8W", "Question": "NEJMoa1206809", "WorkerId": "A3BDVHNMJECSKG", "Qualification": 0.7692307692307693, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 2, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "24-39", "level": 3, "branch": "NEJMoa1206809", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"screen mammography": ["Intervention"], "breast cancer": ["Outcomes"], "woman": ["Participants"], "40": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"screen mammography": ["Intervention-general"], "breast cancer": ["Outcomes-general"], "woman": ["Sex"], "40": ["Age"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "B"], "Outcomes": ["B", "C"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Age": ["A"], "Location": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["B"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1206809_3VAR3R6G1QM8EY428K5P65TT76XO8W", "children": [{"Answer": "Looking at 30 years of sreening mammography, it has only marginally reduced the rate at which women present with advanced breast cancer.", "AssignmentId": "3VZLGYJEYMVAS3JHI1SY22HQIPFZXZ", "Question": "NEJMoa1206809", "WorkerId": "AON59V5VZU2AK", "Qualification": 0.8461538461538461, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 3, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 4, "branch": "NEJMoa1206809", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"breast cancer": ["Outcomes"], "woman": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"breast cancer": ["Outcomes-general"], "woman": ["Sex"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "B"], "Outcomes": ["C", "B"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Age": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["B"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1206809_3VZLGYJEYMVAS3JHI1SY22HQIPFZXZ", "children": [{"Answer": "Screening mammography is helpful for detecting early stage breast cancer.", "AssignmentId": "3QL2OFSM973S8GU3OHLHT2P773ZNC4", "Question": "NEJMoa1206809", "WorkerId": "A2LTOS0AZ3B28A", "Qualification": 0.8461538461538461, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 4, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 5, "branch": "NEJMoa1206809", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"screen mammography": ["Intervention"], "breast cancer": ["Outcomes"], "early stage": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"screen mammography": ["Intervention-general"], "breast cancer": ["Outcomes-general"], "early stage": ["Outcomes-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C"], "Outcomes": ["C", "B"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Age": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1206809_3QL2OFSM973S8GU3OHLHT2P773ZNC4"}]}]}]}]}, {"Answer": "A study was conducted over thirty-two years with the object of comparing the rate of early and late stage breast cancer in women over 40. It was discovered that since mammography screening began in the United States there was a larger number of early stage breast cancer diagnoses. Unfortunately, it was also discovered that a great portion of those diagnoses were actually lumps or tumors that would never have developed into advanced stage breast cancer. This significantly cuts the success rate of mammography screening in the prevention of advanced stage breast cancer. It was estimated that in 2008 alone, that 31 percent of all breast cancer diagnoses were over diagnosed  in this manner. &#13;The overall data accumulated from this study indicates that mammography screening has only a very slight impact on the total death rate attributed to breast cancer, and because of over diagnosing, is actually driving the numbers of early stage breast cancer detected higher than it is. ", "AssignmentId": "3EF8EXOTT2GC2NTKTM45JZPZUSI1JF", "Question": "NEJMoa1206809", "WorkerId": "AUPHYAKC58LPA", "Qualification": 0.46153846153846156, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 0, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "24-39", "level": 1, "branch": "NEJMoa1206809", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"breast cancer": ["Outcomes"], "early stage": ["Outcomes"], "late stage": ["Outcomes"], "woman": ["Participants"], "40": ["Participants"], "united states": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"breast cancer": ["Outcomes-general"], "early stage": ["Outcomes-general"], "late stage": ["Outcomes-general"], "woman": ["Sex"], "40": ["Age"], "united states": ["Location"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "B"], "Outcomes": ["A", "C"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Age": ["A"], "Location": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["B"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1206809_3EF8EXOTT2GC2NTKTM45JZPZUSI1JF", "children": [{"Answer": "This article was to show the effect of three decades of screening mammography on breast cancer incidence. Trends were collected from information from 1976 through until 2008 for this study. It found that for women with late stage breast cancer had decreased by 8% during that time.  Another finding has shown that breast cancer had been overdiagnosed many times. Mammography has been shown to significantly reduce the rate that women present with advanced cancer.", "AssignmentId": "3JZQSN0I3RVT10XRSFYNBO1D3FVGFC", "Question": "NEJMoa1206809", "WorkerId": "A1AZV2XOQK7RSW", "Qualification": 0.7692307692307693, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 1, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 2, "branch": "NEJMoa1206809", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"screen mammography": ["Intervention"], "breast cancer": ["Outcomes"], "three decade": ["Intervention"], "late stage": ["Outcomes"], "woman": ["Participants"], "8 %": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"screen mammography": ["Intervention-general"], "breast cancer": ["Outcomes-general"], "three decade": ["Duration"], "late stage": ["Outcomes-general"], "woman": ["Sex"], "8 %": ["Effect-strength"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["B", "B"], "Conclusion": ["D"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Age": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Effect-strength": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["D"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1206809_3JZQSN0I3RVT10XRSFYNBO1D3FVGFC", "children": [{"Answer": "Reducing mortality requires screening detect life-threatening disease at an earlier, curable stage.  Despite substantial increase in the number of early-stage breast cancer detected, mammography hs only marginally reduced the rate at which women present with advanced cancer.", "AssignmentId": "39GAF6DQWSLLTITEABIOMN0TPUP1VU", "Question": "NEJMoa1206809", "WorkerId": "A2YTQDLACTLIBA", "Qualification": 0.8461538461538461, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 2, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "60+", "level": 3, "branch": "NEJMoa1206809", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"breast cancer": ["Outcomes"], "early stage": ["Outcomes"], "woman": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"breast cancer": ["Outcomes-general"], "early stage": ["Outcomes-general"], "woman": ["Sex"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["B", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C"], "Outcomes": ["A", "C"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["B"], "Age": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1206809_39GAF6DQWSLLTITEABIOMN0TPUP1VU", "children": [{"Answer": "Mammography has only slightly reduced the rate at which women present with advanced rate diagnosed breast cancers.", "AssignmentId": "3Z7EFSHGNAZXKA87QN8QR4G598ECX0", "Question": "NEJMoa1206809", "WorkerId": "A1AZV2XOQK7RSW", "Qualification": 0.7692307692307693, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 3, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 4, "branch": "NEJMoa1206809", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"breast cancer": ["Outcomes"], "woman": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"breast cancer": ["Outcomes-general"], "woman": ["Sex"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B", "C"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Age": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1206809_3Z7EFSHGNAZXKA87QN8QR4G598ECX0", "children": [{"Answer": "Mammography has marginally reduced presentation with advanced cancer.", "AssignmentId": "3AMYWKA6YC7LAKLEF58RMRX22SE6OY", "Question": "NEJMoa1206809", "WorkerId": "A2YTQDLACTLIBA", "Qualification": 0.8461538461538461, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 4, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "60+", "level": 5, "branch": "NEJMoa1206809", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {}, "Fine": {}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C"], "Outcomes": ["C", "B"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Age": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1206809_3AMYWKA6YC7LAKLEF58RMRX22SE6OY"}]}]}]}]}, {"Answer": "For breast cancer treatment to be the most effective, it is necessary for breast cancer to be found at earlier stages. To help further this, research has been done into this topic. The focus of the systematic review was that of trends in detecting breast cancer early, through mammography, from 1976 to 2008. While studies have shown that mammography has been effective at detecting breast cancer in the earlier stages, there were other things the study found as well that give less optimistic results. Taking into account certain trends in overdiagnosis and excesses due to hormone-replacement therapy, it was found that around 31% of breast cancer cases diagnosed in 2008 were overdiagnosed and around 1.3 million cases followed suit in the past 30 years. The researchers in these studies came to the conclusion that screening mammography has not had a large impact on the number of cases that advance to further stages of breast cancer, and consequently little effect on the mortality rate of breast cancer.", "AssignmentId": "3P4RDNWND6RN2TPI1TPBBY6LBUDIJ8", "Question": "NEJMoa1206809", "WorkerId": "A1TMWYZL6USNIF", "Qualification": 0.8461538461538461, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 0, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "24-39", "level": 1, "branch": "NEJMoa1206809", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"screen mammography": ["Intervention"], "breast cancer": ["Outcomes"], "early stage": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"screen mammography": ["Intervention-general"], "breast cancer": ["Outcomes-general"], "early stage": ["Outcomes-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A", "C"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Age": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1206809_3P4RDNWND6RN2TPI1TPBBY6LBUDIJ8", "children": [{"Answer": "Effective use of cancer-screening programs increase the detection rate of early stage cancer, and decreases the incidence of late stage cancer. For the study, 3 different techniques were used to study trends from 1976 through 2008: Surveillance, Epidemiology, and End Results data. Screening mammography has doubled the cases of detected early-stage cancer from 112 to 234 cases for every 100,000 women. The study also found an over diagnosis of breast cancer in women in the past 30 years, once you remove hormone therapy and account for trends.", "AssignmentId": "36U2A8VAG2K43DA5NWBQY10MG79KYN", "Question": "NEJMoa1206809", "WorkerId": "A2WP9EC483LJY4", "Qualification": 0.5384615384615384, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 1, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "24-39", "level": 2, "branch": "NEJMoa1206809", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"screen mammography": ["Intervention"], "breast cancer": ["Outcomes"], "1976 through 2008": ["Intervention"], "early stage": ["Outcomes"], "late stage": ["Outcomes"], "woman": ["Participants"], "double": ["Outcomes"], "112 to 234": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"screen mammography": ["Intervention-general"], "breast cancer": ["Outcomes-general"], "1976 through 2008": ["Duration"], "early stage": ["Outcomes-general"], "late stage": ["Outcomes-general"], "woman": ["Sex"], "double": ["Effect-strength"], "112 to 234": ["Effect-strength"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A", "B"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Age": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1206809_36U2A8VAG2K43DA5NWBQY10MG79KYN", "children": [{"Answer": "The quantity of early stage breast cancer cases discovered has increased with the introduction of Mammography screening. This rate has doubled (50% more) while on the other end, the quantity of late stage breast cancer cases detected had reduced with the mammography by 8%. ", "AssignmentId": "3QIYRE09Y428LDK58KWXC66G3RY1NO", "Question": "NEJMoa1206809", "WorkerId": "ADGH08WUP68ZF", "Qualification": 0.9230769230769231, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 2, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "15-24", "level": 3, "branch": "NEJMoa1206809", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"breast cancer": ["Outcomes"], "early stage": ["Outcomes"], "late stage": ["Outcomes"], "8 %": ["Outcomes"], "double": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"breast cancer": ["Outcomes-general"], "early stage": ["Outcomes-general"], "late stage": ["Outcomes-general"], "8 %": ["Effect-strength"], "double": ["Effect-strength"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C"], "Outcomes": ["A", "A"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Age": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["A"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1206809_3QIYRE09Y428LDK58KWXC66G3RY1NO", "children": [{"Answer": "Screening mammography helps catch early stage breast cancer. Despite that, early screening only reduce the deaths from cancer by 1/3.", "AssignmentId": "3BC8WZX3V4HHTGBEZLSTRHT38S5RRY", "Question": "NEJMoa1206809", "WorkerId": "A2LTOS0AZ3B28A", "Qualification": 0.8461538461538461, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 3, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 4, "branch": "NEJMoa1206809", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"screen mammography": ["Intervention"], "breast cancer": ["Outcomes"], "early stage": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"screen mammography": ["Intervention-general"], "breast cancer": ["Outcomes-general"], "early stage": ["Outcomes-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B", "C"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Age": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1206809_3BC8WZX3V4HHTGBEZLSTRHT38S5RRY", "children": [{"Answer": "Mammography slightly reduced the rate women present with advanced cancer.", "AssignmentId": "3DL65MZB8E0OEAHQVIIY3FVYUCJCES", "Question": "NEJMoa1206809", "WorkerId": "A2ELH7YDLFNJUZ", "Qualification": 1.0, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 4, "Education": "College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "24-39", "level": 5, "branch": "NEJMoa1206809", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"woman": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"woman": ["Sex"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C"], "Outcomes": ["C", "B"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Age": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1206809_3DL65MZB8E0OEAHQVIIY3FVYUCJCES"}]}]}]}]}, {"Answer": "Thirty years of academic study have shown that breast cancer screening programs do not reduce the rate with which women develop advanced cancer. Effective screening must not only increase cancer detection in early stages, but also decrease the incidence of patients developing cancer later. The study used three types of cancer detection data gathered between the years of 1976 and 2008. &#13;Early evidence was promising. Screening mammography in the US has doubled the number of early stage breast cancer patients detected per year. Also, the rate of late stage cancers reported has dropped 8%. However, the incidence of overdiagnosis - for example the finding of non symptomatic tumors - was high, with researchers estimating at least 1.3 million overdiagnosises have occurred in the past 30 years. In 2008 alone, it was estimated that 31% of all breast cancer diagnosises were overdiagnosed. This new information suggests that mammography screening is having a limited effect on the rate of fatal breast cancers. ", "AssignmentId": "3MTMREQS4W3U2V6JW4GDJQCA0KVAW9", "Question": "NEJMoa1206809", "WorkerId": "A1SXNLUT6WM90L", "Qualification": 0.7692307692307693, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 0, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 1, "branch": "NEJMoa1206809", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"screen mammography": ["Intervention"], "breast cancer": ["Outcomes"], "early stage": ["Outcomes"], "late stage": ["Outcomes"], "woman": ["Participants"], "8 %": ["Outcomes"], "double": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"screen mammography": ["Intervention-general"], "breast cancer": ["Outcomes-general"], "early stage": ["Outcomes-general"], "late stage": ["Outcomes-general"], "woman": ["Sex"], "8 %": ["Effect-strength"], "double": ["Effect-strength"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "C", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A", "B"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Age": ["C"], "Location": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1206809_3MTMREQS4W3U2V6JW4GDJQCA0KVAW9", "children": [{"Answer": "Mammography is touted as an effective way to detect breast cancer in women. But, a long-term study suggests there is a substantial over-diagnosis of breast cancer, and that screenings have only marginally reduced the rate of death from the disease. However, regardless of the over-diagnosis, the imbalance suggests cancer-screening programs are still shown to be effective in detecting the disease at an early stage while decreasing the incidence of late stage cancer.", "AssignmentId": "3OS46CRSLGKG04UBGHU5HJRAXVRV6O", "Question": "NEJMoa1206809", "WorkerId": "A2KROBPV0YPE4A", "Qualification": 0.7692307692307693, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 1, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 2, "branch": "NEJMoa1206809", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"breast cancer": ["Outcomes"], "early stage": ["Outcomes"], "late stage": ["Outcomes"], "woman": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"breast cancer": ["Outcomes-general"], "early stage": ["Outcomes-general"], "late stage": ["Outcomes-general"], "woman": ["Sex"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["B", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C"], "Outcomes": ["A", "C"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["B"], "Age": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1206809_3OS46CRSLGKG04UBGHU5HJRAXVRV6O", "children": [{"Answer": "Though screening is in theory an effective method of early diagnosis for breast cancer, some recent studies of data have shown that screening is only having a minor effect when it comes to mortality rates.  This imbalance suggests there are mis-or-over diagnosis occurring. ", "AssignmentId": "32UTUBMZ7HHM6GB6C8BDSZD2B7OVBH", "Question": "NEJMoa1206809", "WorkerId": "AXY0D2AMLKE2A", "Qualification": 0.5384615384615384, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 2, "Education": "College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "24-39", "level": 3, "branch": "NEJMoa1206809", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"breast cancer": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"breast cancer": ["Outcomes-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["B", "C"], "Outcomes": ["C", "B"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Age": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["B"], "Duration": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1206809_32UTUBMZ7HHM6GB6C8BDSZD2B7OVBH", "children": [{"Answer": "Mammograms haven't much reduced the rate of women with advanced breast cancer and only have a small effect on the rate of deaths.", "AssignmentId": "3BXQMRHWK0JICSQ3Y7RHATMD94ZMUY", "Question": "NEJMoa1206809", "WorkerId": "A2YUCJ28XANFOX", "Qualification": 0.7692307692307693, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 3, "Education": "High School", "Gender": "female", "Age": "24-39", "level": 4, "branch": "NEJMoa1206809", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"breast cancer": ["Outcomes"], "woman": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"breast cancer": ["Outcomes-general"], "woman": ["Sex"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B", "C"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Age": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1206809_3BXQMRHWK0JICSQ3Y7RHATMD94ZMUY", "children": [{"Answer": "Mammography has only slightly reduced the rate for advanced cancer.", "AssignmentId": "37UQDCYH6YGZ448GZRZXNXR6TWW7V1", "Question": "NEJMoa1206809", "WorkerId": "A1AZV2XOQK7RSW", "Qualification": 0.7692307692307693, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 4, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 5, "branch": "NEJMoa1206809", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {}, "Fine": {}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B", "C"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Age": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1206809_37UQDCYH6YGZ448GZRZXNXR6TWW7V1"}]}]}]}]}, {"Answer": "An analysis of the incidence of early-stage and late-stage breast cancer among women aged 40 years or older over three decades (from 1976 to 2008) found that breast cancer was overdiagnosed in nearly one-third of all new cases. This equates to roughly 1.3 million women in the United States over the past three decades and more than 70,000 in 2008 alone. The overdiagnosis of breast cancer, defined as the presence of tumors upon screening that would not have led to the presentation of clinical symptoms, is thought to be due, in large part, to the increased use of mammography in clinical practice. While the introduction of mammography within cancer-screening programs in the United States has undoubtedly led to an increase in the detection of early-stage breast cancer, minimal effects have been seen with their use on the rates of advanced breast cancer presentations and mortality attributed to the disease.", "AssignmentId": "39LNWE0K4VHWG90CDSTPI0FWSD0IUZ", "Question": "NEJMoa1206809", "WorkerId": "A3K7OKFT05A073", "Qualification": 1.0, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 0, "Education": "College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "24-39", "level": 1, "branch": "NEJMoa1206809", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"breast cancer": ["Outcomes"], "three decade": ["Intervention"], "early stage": ["Outcomes"], "late stage": ["Outcomes"], "woman": ["Participants"], "40": ["Participants"], "united states": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"breast cancer": ["Outcomes-general"], "three decade": ["Duration"], "early stage": ["Outcomes-general"], "late stage": ["Outcomes-general"], "woman": ["Sex"], "40": ["Age"], "united states": ["Location"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A", "C"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Age": ["A"], "Location": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1206809_39LNWE0K4VHWG90CDSTPI0FWSD0IUZ", "children": [{"Answer": "To decrease the likelihood of death, it is critical that mammography screenings detect life-threatening diseases at an early stage. Data has been examined from 1976 to 2008 in trends with early-stage breast cancer and late-stage breast cancer. Even with the increase in the number of early-stage breast cancer detected, screening mammography has only slightly decreased the rate which women present advanced cancer. Evidence suggests that there is a significant amount of over diagnosis and that screening is only has a minimal affect on death rate. ", "AssignmentId": "3D3VGR7TA10PAEQCOVRX9JQN2YG3R1", "Question": "NEJMoa1206809", "WorkerId": "A3MT4SBSBPER68", "Qualification": 0.46153846153846156, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 1, "Education": "College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "24-39", "level": 2, "branch": "NEJMoa1206809", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"screen mammography": ["Intervention"], "breast cancer": ["Outcomes"], "early stage": ["Outcomes"], "late stage": ["Outcomes"], "woman": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"screen mammography": ["Intervention-general"], "breast cancer": ["Outcomes-general"], "early stage": ["Outcomes-general"], "late stage": ["Outcomes-general"], "woman": ["Sex"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A", "C"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Age": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1206809_3D3VGR7TA10PAEQCOVRX9JQN2YG3R1", "children": [{"Answer": "Decreasing the death rate begins with early detection. The earlier that it is caught, the better the chances of curing are. Cancer screening programs that increase early detection and decrease detection of later stages, are considered effective. ", "AssignmentId": "3DHE4R9OCXW906LF4KJGR57OUM02GA", "Question": "NEJMoa1206809", "WorkerId": "AHYXP6QIMYJLD", "Qualification": 0.6923076923076923, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 2, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "24-39", "level": 3, "branch": "NEJMoa1206809", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {}, "Fine": {}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["B", "C"], "Outcomes": ["C", "B"], "Conclusion": ["C"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Age": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["B"], "Duration": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["C"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1206809_3DHE4R9OCXW906LF4KJGR57OUM02GA", "children": [{"Answer": "Breast cancer early diagnoses have increased in the US, thereby resulting in a decreased incidence of late stage breast cancer.", "AssignmentId": "3A0EX8ZRN993AA6BHJYXZYHWTURBYJ", "Question": "NEJMoa1206809", "WorkerId": "A1E235KE3CSO7H", "Qualification": 0.8461538461538461, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 3, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "60+", "level": 4, "branch": "NEJMoa1206809", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"breast cancer": ["Outcomes"], "late stage": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"breast cancer": ["Outcomes-general"], "late stage": ["Outcomes-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "A"], "Intervention": ["C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["A", "C"], "Conclusion": ["C"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Age": ["C"], "Location": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["C"], "Duration": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["C"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1206809_3A0EX8ZRN993AA6BHJYXZYHWTURBYJ", "children": [{"Answer": "we can detect the starting stage of breast cancer.", "AssignmentId": "3U088ZLJVLEY1I8142JKUK0XSRSW00", "Question": "NEJMoa1206809", "WorkerId": "A3F6TS7I3CSUM8", "Qualification": 0.6923076923076923, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 4, "Education": "College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "24-39", "level": 5, "branch": "NEJMoa1206809", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"breast cancer": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"breast cancer": ["Outcomes-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["C", "C"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Age": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["C"], "Duration": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["C"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1206809_3U088ZLJVLEY1I8142JKUK0XSRSW00"}]}]}]}]}, {"Answer": "To decrease the likelihood of death breast cancer screens should be done early in life so as to catch the disease in the early stages. If done so the breast cancer screen will increase the likelihood that cancer will be detected at earlier ages, but will decrease the prevalence of finding cancer at later more difficult to treat stages. Studies were done on breast cancer screens from 1976 to 2008 among women over 40 years of age. Introduction of mammography in the US has resulted in a increase in detection of breast cancer in women by double, but decreased the number of these detections in the later stage of the disease overall. The rate of decrease in dectections at the later stage of breast cancer was 8%. Excluding data associated with hormone-replacement therapy and data from women diagnosed who were younger than age 40, lead to the finding that breast cancer is over diagnosed in 1.3 million women in the past 30 years.", "AssignmentId": "32VNZTT0A8PASA9GO9WGJOITGWYR4S", "Question": "NEJMoa1206809", "WorkerId": "AWCD7E12GSX2Z", "Qualification": 0.6153846153846154, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 0, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "24-39", "level": 1, "branch": "NEJMoa1206809", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"breast cancer": ["Outcomes"], "early stage": ["Outcomes"], "woman": ["Participants"], "40": ["Participants"], "8 %": ["Outcomes"], "double": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"breast cancer": ["Outcomes-general"], "early stage": ["Outcomes-general"], "woman": ["Sex"], "40": ["Age"], "8 %": ["Effect-strength"], "double": ["Effect-strength"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A", "B"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Age": ["A"], "Location": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1206809_32VNZTT0A8PASA9GO9WGJOITGWYR4S", "children": [{"Answer": "The incidence of of breast cancer in the years between 1976 to 2008 was analyzed in women at and above 40 years old. The quantity of cases detected in early stage breast cancer annually has doubled from 112 to 234 cases for every 100,000 patients with mammography screening in the US. Parallel to this, the quantity of cases detected at late stage breast cancer has dropped by 8 cases for every 100,000 patients. It should be noted that breast cancers are also over diagnosed with this technology. In 2008, 31% of breast cancers were over diagnosed. ", "AssignmentId": "3TXMY6UCAF9DBD7V49DYXWKCCPSQCM", "Question": "NEJMoa1206809", "WorkerId": "ADGH08WUP68ZF", "Qualification": 0.9230769230769231, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 1, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "15-24", "level": 2, "branch": "NEJMoa1206809", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"breast cancer": ["Outcomes"], "early stage": ["Outcomes"], "late stage": ["Outcomes"], "woman": ["Participants"], "40": ["Participants"], "double": ["Outcomes"], "112 to 234": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"breast cancer": ["Outcomes-general"], "early stage": ["Outcomes-general"], "late stage": ["Outcomes-general"], "woman": ["Sex"], "40": ["Age"], "double": ["Effect-strength"], "112 to 234": ["Effect-strength"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A", "A"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Age": ["A"], "Location": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["A"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1206809_3TXMY6UCAF9DBD7V49DYXWKCCPSQCM", "children": [{"Answer": "From the 1976 to 2008 in this stage earlier period of breast cancer, last stage of breast cancer among 40 years of the age or older. screening mammography has only marginally reduced the rate at which women present wit advanced cancer. ", "AssignmentId": "33CID57105EE7GVZJBU1N7HOWHVL3J", "Question": "NEJMoa1206809", "WorkerId": "A3F6TS7I3CSUM8", "Qualification": 0.6923076923076923, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 2, "Education": "College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "24-39", "level": 3, "branch": "NEJMoa1206809", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"screen mammography": ["Intervention"], "breast cancer": ["Outcomes"], "woman": ["Participants"], "40": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"screen mammography": ["Intervention-general"], "breast cancer": ["Outcomes-general"], "woman": ["Sex"], "40": ["Age"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A", "C"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Age": ["A"], "Location": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1206809_33CID57105EE7GVZJBU1N7HOWHVL3J", "children": [{"Answer": "Effective screening for early stage breast cancer has led to an increase of detecting early stage cancer yet does not effect death rates.", "AssignmentId": "3SBEHTYCWOODXIKHNTQELLL9OKLIY9", "Question": "NEJMoa1206809", "WorkerId": "A35F1LYW2ZXWLT", "Qualification": 0.6153846153846154, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 3, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "24-39", "level": 4, "branch": "NEJMoa1206809", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"breast cancer": ["Outcomes"], "early stage": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"breast cancer": ["Outcomes-general"], "early stage": ["Outcomes-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["B", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B", "C"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Age": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["B"], "Duration": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1206809_3SBEHTYCWOODXIKHNTQELLL9OKLIY9", "children": [{"Answer": "Breast cancer screening is more effective at detection of early stage.", "AssignmentId": "3G0WWMR1UW5W2H4MTZMCD7EOCJMQN1", "Question": "NEJMoa1206809", "WorkerId": "AVBRJBJONL47I", "Qualification": 0.9230769230769231, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 4, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 5, "branch": "NEJMoa1206809", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"breast cancer": ["Outcomes"], "early stage": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"breast cancer": ["Outcomes-general"], "early stage": ["Outcomes-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B", "C"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Age": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1206809_3G0WWMR1UW5W2H4MTZMCD7EOCJMQN1"}]}]}]}]}, {"Answer": "Cancer screening programs are vital for early detection which is vital for reducing lives lost to breast cancer. They are constantly researching cancer and studying from the past 40 years to help eradicate breast cancer. They are constantly seeking knowledge in order to find more ways to stop cancer. Mammograms have significantly increased the early detection rates, which is a good thing. The rate at which women present with late stage breast cancer has decreased quite a bit. While there is still no cure, women are being treated earlier and thus are becoming cancer free and living at higher rates, than in previous years. Breast cancer has been commonly misdiagnosed because of the presence of benign tumors and similar issues, some caused by hormone replacement therapy. So the statistics about diagnoses, are not as accurate as they may seem at first glance. There is still a long way to go to lower the rate of late stage detection. Screening only has a small effect on the death rate. ", "AssignmentId": "3SLE99ER0OY3F0GGD50GD5QYZ6WBZB", "Question": "NEJMoa1206809", "WorkerId": "AHYXP6QIMYJLD", "Qualification": 0.6923076923076923, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 0, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "24-39", "level": 1, "branch": "NEJMoa1206809", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"breast cancer": ["Outcomes"], "late stage": ["Outcomes"], "woman": ["Participants"], "40": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"breast cancer": ["Outcomes-general"], "late stage": ["Outcomes-general"], "woman": ["Sex"], "40": ["Age"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "D"], "Outcomes": ["A", "C"], "Conclusion": ["D"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Age": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["D"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["D"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1206809_3SLE99ER0OY3F0GGD50GD5QYZ6WBZB", "children": [{"Answer": "Surveillance, Epidemiology, and end result data were used to examine trends from 1976-2008 in the incidents of early stage breast cancer and late stage breast cancer in women 40 years old and older. The results were that in 30 years of breast cancer screening and detection 1.3 million U.S. women were over-diagnosed with breast cancer. In 2008 breast cancer was over-diagnosed in over 70,000 women, which accounted for 31% of all breast cancer diagnoses.This means that screening mammography only slightly reduces the rate of presenting with cancer.", "AssignmentId": "34HJIJKLP6H2LHQXXT1QKL7W1594V2", "Question": "NEJMoa1206809", "WorkerId": "A3CDWPBKYDDASL", "Qualification": 0.8461538461538461, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 1, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "24-39", "level": 2, "branch": "NEJMoa1206809", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"screen mammography": ["Intervention"], "breast cancer": ["Outcomes"], "early stage": ["Outcomes"], "late stage": ["Outcomes"], "woman": ["Participants"], "40": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"screen mammography": ["Intervention-general"], "breast cancer": ["Outcomes-general"], "early stage": ["Outcomes-general"], "late stage": ["Outcomes-general"], "woman": ["Sex"], "40": ["Age"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A", "C"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Age": ["A"], "Location": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1206809_34HJIJKLP6H2LHQXXT1QKL7W1594V2", "children": [{"Answer": "The effectiveness of breast cancer screening through mammography was studied over a 32 year period among women over 40. The results showed there was a substantial rate of over diagnosis, and a minimal effect on mortality rates. ", "AssignmentId": "3RJSC4XJ11F4OZTH81WB4KNK7G850J", "Question": "NEJMoa1206809", "WorkerId": "AUPHYAKC58LPA", "Qualification": 0.46153846153846156, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 2, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "24-39", "level": 3, "branch": "NEJMoa1206809", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"breast cancer": ["Outcomes"], "woman": ["Participants"], "40": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"breast cancer": ["Outcomes-general"], "woman": ["Sex"], "40": ["Age"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "C"], "Intervention": ["B", "A"], "Outcomes": ["B", "C"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Age": ["A"], "Location": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["B"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1206809_3RJSC4XJ11F4OZTH81WB4KNK7G850J", "children": [{"Answer": "Early mammograms have been identifying cancer at a more frequent rate, but deaths from breast cancer have not significantly declined.", "AssignmentId": "3A1COHJ8NKGYMHIF47AZMWWSVT78HY", "Question": "NEJMoa1206809", "WorkerId": "A83OOIGU4606R", "Qualification": 0.9230769230769231, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 3, "Education": "College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "24-39", "level": 4, "branch": "NEJMoa1206809", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"breast cancer": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"breast cancer": ["Outcomes-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C"], "Outcomes": ["C", "B"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Age": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1206809_3A1COHJ8NKGYMHIF47AZMWWSVT78HY", "children": [{"Answer": "Early-stage breast cancer detection hardly reduces advanced cancer results.", "AssignmentId": "36DSNE9QZ6JXYF0LZO2GVV27OY0OJO", "Question": "NEJMoa1206809", "WorkerId": "A3P57IUDHUKNCE", "Qualification": 0.9230769230769231, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 4, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "24-39", "level": 5, "branch": "NEJMoa1206809", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"breast cancer": ["Outcomes"], "early stage": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"breast cancer": ["Outcomes-general"], "early stage": ["Outcomes-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["A", "C"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Age": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["C"], "Duration": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1206809_36DSNE9QZ6JXYF0LZO2GVV27OY0OJO"}]}]}]}]}]}